Hello. My name is Matt,
大家好 我叫 Matt
a Content Developer here at Udacity.
是优达学城的课程开发专家
I wanted to take a few minutes to talk with you about LinkedIn and networking.
我想花几分钟和大家聊聊领英和拓展人脉
Networking is an essential and effective way to meet
拓展人脉是一种关键而有效的方法
and keep in touch with other people who share your interests.
想要结实志同道合的人并与他们保持联系
Whether you're connecting with thought leaders in
无论是结交自己领域的思想领袖
your career field or being a mentor to others,
还是担任新人的导师
networking has the ability to raise your visibility to
拓展人脉都使你更易被雇主
job recruiters and others looking to use your skills collaboratively.
和其他愿意与你合作互助的人看到
You may be actively working toward a promotion or you're looking for your first job.
或许你正在为升职奋斗 或正在寻找第一份工作
Some of you may also be trying to change into
有些人也许正努力转行
career paths and break into a completely new industry.
即将进入一个完全陌生的领域
Wherever you may be in your career path,
无论在职业生涯的哪个节点
networking is the key to getting a great job that will fulfill you,
拓展人脉都十分关键 能使你获得理想的工作
be more challenging, pay more or meet whatever your goals may be.
获得成就感、挑战、加薪或达成其他目标
We all know the importance of the resume in finding a new job and how
我们都知道简历对找到新工作有多重要
crucial the first impression is to presenting yourself to interviewers and recruiters.
在雇主和面试官面前呈现的第一印象有多关键
LinkedIn provides a solution to both of these issues and more.
领英不仅为这些问题提供了解决方案
LinkedIn has become one of
它已经成为你最重要的工具之一
the most important tools you need to have when looking for a new job,
助你寻找新工作、
expanding your network, helping people,
拓展人际关系网、帮助他人、
discovering more events or heightening your brand and presence in the industry.
发现更多机遇、提高品牌在行业的辨识度和存在感
When it comes to networking,
说到拓展人脉
you may have gotten advice to grow your network,
也许有人建议过你扩大社交圈
but may not know the strategies to do so.
但你不知道用什么策略扩大
This lesson is about giving you that missing strategy so that you can
这门课会告诉你一些需要的策略 你就可以
expand your LinkedIn profile to help you in your networking goals.
扩大领英账号影响力 实现社交目标
Back when I was looking for a new career before Udacity,
加入优达前 我也在寻找一份新的事业
I resisted the idea of using my LinkedIn account during the job search.
那时我抵触用领英账号找工作的想法
Connecting with people I didn't know was really awkward and frustrating.
结交不认识的人让我感到尴尬和沮丧
I thought that my time and energy would be better spent making sure my resume was
我认为时间和精力花在确保简历完美
perfect or that I was ready for those interviews that would one day I had my way.
或准备哪些总有一天会到来的面试 会比较有效
Investing time into LinkedIn seem like a huge burden.
花时间在领英上感觉是个大负担
However, I learned later that using LinkedIn
然而 我之后才明白用领英
actually has a benefit of connecting me with peers and sharing knowledge,
有结识同辈 分享知识的好处
helping me keep up to date on changes and innovation within my career field and opens
能帮助我紧跟职业领域内的变化和创新
me up to many career opportunities not available from other sources like job boards.
并打开其他求职平台上找不到的职业机遇